Hi!
This is John again.
Now, let’s talk about the hardness of the bullets we are casting.
This bullet here was cast with a combination of wheel weights, tin, and antimony.
What you can do is get the blend that you need from a commercial source to use with your wheel weights.
This will make your bullets harder.
This bullet here has more lead content in it.
I can tell by being able to scratch the surface of the bullet and you can see you where you scratched.
In this bullet you cannot do that.
There is something called a Brinell hardness of bullet.
This bullet has about a 22 Brinell hardness.
This bullet here has about 10 hardness on it.
This is meant to be driven at lower velocities than this bullet.